邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can! Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
He hasn't been home in a few days.
我觉得他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
拯救人类 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
saving people, hunting things.Family business.
你觉得妈妈想让我们这样
You think Mom would have wanted this for us?
- 我无法一个人完成 - 我开车
- I can't do this alone. - l'm driving.
（罗斯福收容所 罗克福德 伊利诺斯州）
孩子们总是不听话闯进去
Can't keep kids out of this place.
那又怎么样
What is it anyway?
我忘了你不是本地人
l forgot you're not local.
- 你不知道这个传说 - 传说？
- You don't know the legend. - Legend?
每个小镇都有自己的传说 不是吗？
Every town's got its stories, right?
我们的就是这罗斯福收容所
Ours is Roosevelt Asylum.
他们说这里有病人的鬼魂出现
They say it's haunted with the ghosts of the patients.
在这里过夜 鬼魂会把你逼疯
Spend the night, the spirits will drive you insane.
有人吗 警察
Hello? Police officers!
警察
Police officers!
这些孩子带着断线钳？
You telling me these kids brought bolt cutters?
来吧
Come on.
我们分头找
we'll split up.
好的
All right.
有人吗？
Hello?
好了
All right.
给我出来
Come on out.
凯莉 听到请回话？
Kelly, you copy?
靠 你去哪里了
Jeez.Where the hell you been?
里面
ln there.
有什么 看到什么吗
What was it? See anything?
没什么
No.
这是巡逻1- 4 任务完成 正往回赶
This is patrol 1-4. We are clear and returning to station.
罗杰 巡逻1- 4
Roger, Patrol 1-4…
嘿
Hey.
怎么了 你还是不和我说话吗
, what? You're still not talking to me?
沃尔特 我为以前所做的道歉
Walt, I said I was sorry about before.
要我说多少遍？
How many times do I have to say it?
《邪恶力量》
不 上次我们收到信 他还在加州
No, Dad was in California last we heard from him.
我们只是想 他会来找你要军火
We just thought that he comes to you for munitions…
也许你在最近几个星期见过他
maybe you seen him in the last few weeks.
- 如果你听到什么一定要告诉我 - 谢谢
- Call us if you hear anything - Thanks.
凯尔博也没有他的消息吗？
Caleb hasn't heard from him?
杰斐逊和吉姆牧师也不知道
Nope. Neither has Jefferson or Pastor Jim.
在日记里发现什么吗？
What about the journal?
发现什么吗？
Any leads in there?
没有 和我上次翻过一样
No. Same last time I looked.
我什么也找不出来
Nothing I can make out.
我喜欢这个家伙
I love the guy.
我发誓他有点象「尤达」大师
But he writes like Yoda.
也许我们该去找联邦调查局 贴出寻人启事
Maybe we should call the feds. File a missing persons.
爸爸如果知道我们让联邦调查局介入 他会发怒的
We talked about this. Dad would be pissed if we put the feds on him.
在堪萨斯州发生的那件事
I don't care. After all that happened back in Kansas…
他当时应该在那里
He should've been there.
你也这么说
You said so yourself.
你试着打给他可什么都没有
You tried to call him.
我知道
I know.
我的手机在哪里
Where the hell is my cell phone?
你知道吗 根据我们现在情况他可能死了
You know, he could be dead.
不准这么说
Don't say that.
他没有死 他只是
He's not dead.He's-He's.
他怎么了？
He's what?
躲了起来？他很忙吗？
He's hiding? He's busy?
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
什么？
What?
是个短消息
It's a A text message.
是个坐标值
It's coordinates.
你觉得爸爸在考验我们？
You think Dad was texting us?
他以前也给过我们坐标
He's given us coordinates before.
这个消息没什么值得庆祝的 迪恩
He can barely work a toaster, Dean.
萨姆 这是个好消息
Sam, this is good news. It means he's okay.
这意味着他没事
Or alive, at least.
还活着 发消息的人有电话号码吗？
Was there a number on the caller ID?
上面的显示是「不明」
No, it said unknown.
好吧 那么坐标点在那里？
Where do the coordinates point?
这正是有趣的地方
That's the interesting part.
罗克福德 伊利诺斯州
Rockford, lllinois.
好 这有趣在哪里？
Okay, and that's interesting how?
我查了下罗克福德当地的报纸 看看这个
I checked the local Rockford paper. Take a look at this.
这个警察沃尔特 凯莉 轮班回家后
This cop, Walter Kelly, he comes home from his shift.
射杀了他的妻子
Shoots his wife…
然后把枪对着自己的嘴
then puts the gun in his mouth.
把脑子都轰了出来
Blows his brains out.
当天晚上早些时候
Earlier that night.
凯莉和搭档接到 让他们去罗斯福收容所的电话
Kelly and his partner responded to a call at Roosevelt Asylum.
我还是不能理解
Okay, l'm not following.
这和我们有什么关系？
What does this have to do with us?
爸爸在日记里给同样的收容所打上了标记
Dad earmarked the same asylum in the journal.
让我们看看
Let's see.
这里七人目击
Here. Seven unconfirmed sightings.
两人死亡
Two deaths.
直到上周 至少
Till last week, at least.
我想这就是他想让我们去的地方
I think this is where he wants us to go.
这只是个工作
This is a job.
爸爸只是想让我们去完成它
Dad wants us to work a job.
是的 也许我们能见到他 也许他就在那里
Yeah, maybe we'll meet up with him.
他也许只是想让我们去猎鬼而已
He could be sending us there by ourselves to hunt this thing.
谁管呢？
Who cares?
如果他希望我们去那里 这对我来说就足够了
lf he wants us there, it's good enough for me.
这不让你奇怪吗
This doesn't strike you as weird?
考验 坐标
The texting? The coordinates?
萨姆
Sam.
爸爸叫我们去那里 我们就去
Dad's telling us to go somewhere. We're going.
你好 你就是丹尼尔·冈德森 对吧 警察
You're Daniel Gunderson, right? You're a cop?
是的
Yeah.
我是芝加哥报的奈杰尔·塔夫诺
I'm Nigel Tufnel, with the Chicago Tribune.
你不介意我问一些关于你搭档的问题吧？
Mind if I ask a couple questions about your partner?
不 我介意
Yeah, I do.
我只想在这里喝瓶啤酒
I'm just trying to have a beer.
我想听听你说说这故事
It won't take that long. I just wanna hear your story.
一星期前 我的搭档就坐在这个位置
A week ago my partner was sitting in that chair.
现在他死了
Now he's dead.
你是故意在这里等我吗？
You gonna ambush me here?
对不起 我只想知道发生了什么
Sorry. I need to know what happened.
离他远点
Hey, buddy. How about leaving the guy alone, huh?
他可是个警察
The man's an officer.
你为什么不表现得尊重一点
Why don't you show a little respect.
你不必那么做
You didn't have to do that.
不 我得那样
Yeah, of course I did.
那家伙是个混蛋
That guy's a serious jerk.
让我请你喝一杯
Let me buy you a beer, huh?
两杯
Two.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在那推我可够猛的
You shoved me kind of hard in there.
我得那么做 不是吗？
l had to sell it, didn't l?
这可是情景表演
It's Method acting.
什么？
Huh?
算了
Never mind.
你从冈德森查到什么？
What'd you find out from Gunderson?
沃尔特 凯莉是个好警察
Walter Kelly was a good cop.
已经是个小头头
Head of his class, evenkeeled.
而且前途一片光明
He had a bright future ahead of him.
那他家里呢？
What about at home?
他和老婆常常吵些小架
He and his wife had a few fights.
但日子还算平稳
But it was mostly smooth sailing.
他们甚至考虑过要孩子
They were talking about having kids.
所以凯莉要么是忍不住爆发了
So either Kelly had some crazy waiting to bust out…
或是另有原因
or something did it to him. Right.
关于收容所 冈德森说了什么？
What'd Gunderson tell you about the asylum?
很多
A lot.
很明显 警察追捕孩子来到了这
So apparently, the cops chased the kids here…
进入房子的南向的房间
into the south wing.
南向的房间
South wing, huh?
等等
Wait a second.
南向的房间 南向的房间
South wing, south wing.
1972年三个孩子进到南向的房间
1 972."Three kids broke into the south wing.
只有一个活了下来
Only one survived."
他是这么说的
Way he tells it.
他的一个朋友发疯 开始放火焚烧房子
one of his friends went nuts and started lighting up the place.
所以无论是发生了什么
So whatever's going on.
南向的房间看来是问题的关键
South wing seems like the heart of it.
但如果孩子们来这收容所探险的话
But if kids are spelunking the asylum.
为什么他们会没事呢？
Why aren't there a ton more deaths?
看起来这门常常被锁着
Looks like the doors are usually chained.
也许锁上有好些年了
Could've been chained up for years.
防止人类进去 或让某东西进去
Yeah, to keep people out. Or to keep something in.
如果你看到死人的话 海利·乔
Let me know if you see any dead people, Haley Joel.
伙计 玩笑开够了
Dude, enough.
我可是认真的
I'm serious.
你得小心点哦
You gotta be careful, all right?
鬼怪们都被你身上类似ESP（鬼魂的感应装置）的东西所吸引
Ghosts are attracted to that ESP thing you got.
我告诉你 这不是ESP
I told you, it's not ESP.
有时我只是有预感 奇怪的梦
I just have strange vibes sometimes.
无论怎么样 不需要的话就不必说出来
Weird dreams. Yeah, whatever. Don't ask, don't tell.
你用那个东西发现些什么没？
You getting any reading on that thing?
没有 当然它并不意味着没人在这里
Nope. It doesn't mean nobody's home.
有些时候鬼魂并不显身
Spirits can't appear during certain hours of the day.
那些家伙在晚上出现
Freaks come out at night.
顺便问问这中间你认为谁最变态啊？
Yeah. Hey, who's the hotter psychic?
帕特丽夏·阿奎特爱上休伊特的珍妮弗还是你？
Patricia Arquette, Jennifer Love Hewitt or you?
伙计
Man.
电击疗法 脑叶切开术
Electroshock, lobotomies.
他们对这些病人的确做痛苦的事
They did some twisted stuff to these people.
对象我这样的人 在「布谷鸟的巢穴」的Jack
Kind of like my man Jack in Cuckoo's Nest.
对此你怎么看？
So, what do you think?
鬼魂控制了人类？
Ghosts are possessing people?
也许
Maybe.
也许更象是在阴宅或者幻觉辐射
Or maybe it's more like Like Amityville or the Smurl haunting.
鬼魂把他们避疯
Spirits driving them insane.
对就象我这样的人 「闪光中的」杰克
Kind of like my man Jack in The Shining.
迪恩
Dean?
我们什么时候才谈谈？
When are we gonna talk about it?
谈什么？
About what?
爸爸不在这里的事实
About the fact that Dad's not here.
让我想想 永远别提
Oh, let's see. Never.
我是认真的 兄弟
l'm being serious, man.
我也是 萨姆 他派我们来这里
So am l, Sam. He sent us here.
他明显想要我们来这里
He obviously wants us here.
我们必要要来这里搜索情况
We'll pick up the search later.
他想要怎么样并不重要
lt doesn't matter what he wants.
看看 就是你这样的态度
See, that attitude right there?
这就是为什么老爸从小对我好些
That is why I always got the extra cookie.
爸爸也许正在危险中
Dad could be in trouble.
我们应该是去找他
We should be looking for him.
我们需要找到答案 迪恩
We deserve answers, Dean.
这可是我们的家人
This is our family.
我能理解 萨姆
I understand that, Sam.
但这是他给我们的命令
But he's given us an order.
那我们就必须遵守这个命令？
We gotta always follow Dad's orders?
当然我们必须
Of course we do.
我必须要查出关于南向房间的更多情况
You know what we gotta do. We gotta find out more about the south wing.
看看是否真有事发生
See if something happened here.
萨姆·温彻斯特？
Sam Winchester?
是我
That's me.
进来吧
Come on in.
谢谢你给我最好一点时间
Thanks for seeing me last minute.
埃利科特医生
Dr. Ellicott?
埃利科特 这个名字
Ellicott, that name.
这里有位桑福德·埃利科特吗？
Wasn't there a? A Dr. Sanford Ellicott?
是的 他好象是位精神病学的专家
Yeah, he was a chief psychiatrist somewhere.
我父亲原来是老罗斯福收容所的院长
My father was chief of staff at the old Roosevelt Asylum.
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
我是个对当地历史比较感兴趣的家伙
Uh, well, l'm sort of a localhistory buff.
那所医院 有事故或其它什么的
Hey, wasn't there a Wasn't there an incident or something? In the hospital.
我猜在南边的房子里 对吗？
l guess. In the south wing, right?
可我们在花你的钱 萨姆
We're on your dollar, Sam.
我们在这里是在谈论你
We're here to talk about you.
好 是的 好的
Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, sure.
所以 现在怎么样？
So. So. How's things?
一切都好 医生
Uh, things are good, doctor.
很好
Good.
那你在做什么呢？
What you been doing?
没什么变化
Uh, same old.
我和哥哥在汽车旅行
Just been on a road trip with my brother.
那有趣吗？
Was that fun?
想想
Loads.
你知道
Um, you know.
我们遇到了很多 有趣的人
We met a lot of…interesting people. Mmhm.
做了很多 很多有趣的事
Did a lot of… A lot of interesting things.
你知道
Uh…You know.
在南向房子里 究竟发生了什么？
What was it exactly that happened in the south wing?
我只是忘记需要提醒
I forget.
听着 如果你热心于当地的历史
If you're a local-history buff.
那关于罗斯福收容所的骚乱 你不可能不知道
Then you know all about the Roosevelt riot.
骚乱？
The riot?
不 我知道 我只是好奇
Well, no, I know. I'm just curious.
萨姆 我们别在逗圈子了 好吗
Sam. Let's cut the bull, shall we?
你在逃避议题
You're avoiding the subject.
什么议题？
What subject?
你
You.
现在我们做个买卖
Now, l'll make you a deal.
我就告诉你那场罗斯福收容所骚乱
I'll tell you all about the Roosevelt riot…
如果你诚实的告诉我你的事
If you tell me something honest about yourself.
比如你可以说说和你一起汽车旅行的哥哥
Like, this brother you're road-tripping with.
你对他怎么想的？
How do you feel about him?
伙计
Dude.
你在那里待了有一辈子了
You were in there forever.
你们究竟在说什么？
What the hell were you talking about?
医学的问话 你也知道
Just the hospital, you know?
还有？还有南向的房间
And? And the south wing?
那里是他们关最棘手的人的地方
It's where they housed the real hard cases.
精神病 发狂的疯子
The psychotics, the criminally insane.
听起来不错哦
Sounds cozy.
在64年的一天晚上 他们发动了骚乱
Yeah. And one night in '64, they rioted.
袭击医生 也互相袭击
Attacked staff, attacked each other.
因此病人控制了收容所
So the patients took over the asylum?
- 很显然 - 有人死了吗？
- Apparently. - Any deaths?
一些病人 也有医生
Some patients, some staff.
我猜想当时一定非常血腥
I guess it was pretty gory.
有些人的尸体一直没被找到
Some of the bodies were never even recovered…
包括院长埃利科特
including our chief of staff, Ellicott.
「没被找到」什么意思？警察搜遍了整个地方
Never recovered? Cops scoured every inch of the place.
但我猜想病人把他的尸体
But I guess the patients must've…
藏到了某处
stuffed the bodies somewhere hidden.
- 那太狠了 - 是的
- That's grim. - Yeah.
是的 他们把所有活着的病人都转移了
So they transferred all the surviving patients.
并关闭了收容所
and shut down the hospital.
看这里有暴力死亡和未发现的尸体
So we've got violent deaths and unrecovered bodies.
这意味着那有着一群鬼魂
Which could mean angry spirits.
不太妙
Good times.
我们晚上再去那里查查看
Let's check out the hospital tonight.
看看这个
Check this out.
冷战
Creepy.
也很可怕
Yet terrifying.
我觉得我们在看电影一样
I thought we were going to a movie.
比那个感觉更真实
This is better.
我们就像是在电影里
It's like we're in a movie.
我不敢相信这就是你对我说的约会
I can't believe you call this a date.
来吧 会很好玩的 让我们看看
Come on, it'll be fun. Let's look around.
来吧
Come on.
那是什么？
What's that? Oh! Oh!
看看
Hey, look.
来吧 我们去看看
Come on, let's check it out.
我不想过去
I don't want to.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
来吧
Come on.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
你在这等一会
You can wait here.
加文 不
W Gavin, no.
我只过去一小会
l'm just gonna be a minute.
这里没什么的 我保证
Nothing's gonna get you, promise.
该死
Damn it.
亲爱的 不是很害怕吗？
Hey, sweetie. Couldn't take it, huh?
嘿
Hey.
加文 你在那里？
Gavin, where are you?
加文
Gavin!
有什么显示吗？
Getting readings?
看来有大件事要发生
Yeah, big time.
这个地方看来疯子成群
This place is orbing like crazy.
在这周围一定有好多鬼魂出没
Probably spirits out and about.
这些没发现的尸体就是因为鬼魂出没？
If these bodies are causing the haunting…
我们去找到并烧了他们
We gotta find them and burn them. Be careful.
这次让我紧张的 不是愤怒的鬼魂
Only thing that makes me more nervous than a pissed-off spirit.
而是愤怒的心理变态的鬼魂
is the pissed-off spirit of a psycho killer.
迪恩 迪恩
Dean. Dean!
霰弹枪迪恩
Shotgun!Dean.
霰弹枪 迪恩
Shotgun! Dean.
萨姆 趴下
Sam, get down!
很奇怪
That was weird.
是的 就你知道
Yeah, you're telling me.
不 迪恩
No, Dean.
我是指她并不是要袭击我
I mean, it was weird that she didn't attack me.
从我刚才的位置她没有任何暴力动作
Looked pretty agro from where I was standing.
她没伤害我
She didn't hurt me.
她甚至都没有那意思
She didn't even try.
如果她不想伤害我
So if she didn't want to hurt me.
那她想做什么？
Then what did she want?
没事 我们不会伤害你
It's all right. We're not gonna hurt you.
没事
It's okay.
你叫什么？
What's your name?
凯瑟琳·凯特
Katherine. Okay.
我的迪恩 这是萨姆
l'm Dean. This is Sam.
你在这里干吗？
What are you doing here?
我男朋友加文
Um, my boyfriend, Gavin.
他也在这里？
ls he here?
某个房间
Somewhere.
他觉得来看看鬼魂也许比较有意思
He thought it would be fun and try and see some ghosts.
我原以为这不过是个
I thought it was all just…
你知道 假装的恶作剧
you know, pretend.
可我看到了东西
I've seen things.
我也听到加文在大叫
I heard Gavin scream and…
好的 凯特来吧
All right. Kat, come on. Sam's gonna get you out…
萨姆会带你出去 然后我们去找你男朋友
and then we'll find your boyfriend.
不 不
No, no.
没找到加文 我不会离开
I'm not gonna leave without Gavin.
我和你们一起去
I'm coming with you.
这不是开玩笑的
It's no joke around here.
这很危险
It's dangerous.
这也是我为什么去找的理由
That's why I've gotta find him.
好吧 那我们分头去找
All right, I guess we're gonna split up, then.
走吧
Let's go.
加文
Gavin!
Gavin?
加文
Gavin!
我有个问题
Hey, I got a question for you.
你一定看过很多恐怖电影 是吗
You've seen a lot of horror movies, yeah?
我想是的
l guess so.
帮我个忙 下次你再看的时候 注意
Do me a favor. Next time you see one, pay attention.
如果有人说某地鬼魂出没
When someone says a place is haunted.
千万不要去
Don't go in.
加文
Gavin.
嘿 加文
Hey, Gavin.
没事 没事了
Hey, it's okay, it's okay.
我是来帮你
I'm here to help…
你是谁？
Who are you?
我叫萨姆
My name is Sam.
我们找到你女朋友 凯特
We found your girlfriend. Kat?
她还好吧？
Yeah. ls she all right?
她很担心你
She's worried about you.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
我拼命的跑
I was running.
我想是摔倒了
l think I fell.
为什么你要跑？
You were running from what?
这有
There was.
有个女孩
There was this girl.
她 她的脸
Her face.
我都有点搞混了
lt was all messed up.
好的 听着 这女孩
Okay, okay. Listen, listen.T.
她想伤害你吗？
his girl, did she try to hurt you?
什么？
What?
不 她
No. She…
她怎么？
She what?
她亲了我一下
She kissed me.
但她并没有伤害你？
Um… But- But she didn't hurt you physically?
伙计 她只是亲了我
Dude, she kissed me.
我只是吓坏了
I'm scarred for life.
相信我 事情可能比你想的要糟糕
Well, trust me, it could've been worse. Now.
你现在还记得其它的什么吗？
Do you remember anything else?
她
She.
实际上 她想和我悄悄说点什么
Actually, she tried to whisper something in my ear.
什么
What?
我也不知道 我吓得跑的飞快
I don't know. I ran like hell.
去他妈的
You son of a bitch.
没事 我有打火机
It's all right. I got a lighter.
你弄疼我的胳膊了
Ow. You're hurting my arm.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
凯特
Kat!
放我出去 求求你
Let me out, please.
凯特 坚持住
Kat, hang on!
- 怎么了？- 她被一个魂抓进去了
- What's going on? - She's with one of them.
- 救我 - 凯特
- Help me! - Kat!
放我出去
Get me out of here!
凯特 他不会伤害你
Kat.It's not gonna hurt you!
听我说 你必须冷静面对他
Listen to me! You have to face it.You have to calm down.
她要做什么？
She's gotta what?
我要做什么？
l have to what?
精神 他们不会伤害我们 他们只是想交流
The spirits. They're not hurting us.They're trying to communicate.
你得面对他
You gotta face it.
你来面对试试
You face it!
这是你出去的唯一办法
No. It's the only way to get out.
看着他 就是这样
Look at it, that's all.
来 你能做到的
Come on, you can do it.
凯特？
Kat?
我希望你是正确的
Man, I hope you're right about this.
是的 我也希望
Yeah, me too.
噢 凯特
Oh. Kat.
- 137 - 你说什么？
- One thirty-seven. - Sorry?
让它在我的耳边低声说 1 37
It whispered in my ear, 1 37.
房间号码
Room number.
如果这些鬼魂不是想伤害人类
So if these spirits aren't trying to hurt anyone.
那么他们想干吗？
Then what are they trying to do?
也许这就是他们想告诉我们的东西
Maybe they've been trying to tell us.
我想我们会找出答案
I guess we'll find out.
好吧
All right.
你们准备好离开这里了吧？
So… Now, you guys ready to leave this place?
这不用说啊
That's an understatement.
好的 你带他们出去
Okay. You get them out of here.
我去找137号房间
I'm gonna go find room 1 37.
你们怎么知道鬼魂这类东西的？
So how do you guys know about all this ghost stuff?
这是我们的工作
It's kind of our job.
人是为了什么理由做这样的工作？
Why would anyone want a job like that?
有个蹩脚的家伙指挥我们这样
I had a crappy guidance counselor.
迪恩？
And Dean?
他是你的老板？
He's your boss?
不
No.
哦
All right.
我想我们有问题要解决了
l think we have a small problem.
让我们打开它
Break it down.
我想这不太可能
l don't think that'll work.
那么从窗户呢
Then a window.
他们也被钉死了
They're barred.
那我们怎么出去？
Well, how are we supposed to get out?
这就是关键
That's the point.
我们现在不能
We're not.
这里有着某种东西
There's something in here.
他们不想让我们离开
It doesn't want us to leave.
那些病人吗
Those patients.
不
No.
另外的东西
Something else.
这就是我为什么每次都能拿大奖
This is why I get paid the big bucks.
「病人日记」
Patients journal.
埃利科特医生没日没夜的工作 让他心理有问题
Why all work and no play makes Dr. Ellicott a very dull boy.
我把这周围都看过了
All right. l've looked everywhere.
没有出路
There's no other way out.
那我们要做什么？
What the hell are we gonna do?
首先我们不能恐惧
We're not gonna panic.
为什么不？
Why the hell not?
萨姆 是我
Hey. Sam, it's me.
我听出来了
I see it.
他在向我走来
It's coming at me.
你在那里？
Where are you?
- 在地下室 快点 - 我马上来
- I'm in the basement. Hurry! - l'm on my way.
你们谁会用霰弹枪？
All right. Can either of you handle a shotgun?
什么 不
What? No.
我行
l can.
我爸带我去打过几次双向飞碟
My dad took me skeet shooting.
里面装的是盐块
All right, here.
它可能杀不了鬼魂
It's loaded with rock salt.
但能驱散它们 如果你看到什么就射击
It'll repel a spirit. So if you see something, shoot.
好的
Okay.
迪恩
Dean!
Dean?
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
我会让你感觉更舒服
I'm going to make you all better.
嘿 加文
Hey, Gavin?
什么事？
Yeah?
如果我们能活着出去
If we make it out of here alive…
我们马上就分手
we are so breaking up.
你听到了吗？
Did you hear that?
什么东西过来了
Something's coming.
他妈的 他妈的
Damn it, damn it!
别开枪 是我
Don't shoot…it's me!
对不起 对不起
Sorry, sorry.
我靠
Son of a…
你们还在这里干吗？
What are you still doing here?
萨姆在那里？
Where's Sam?
他去了地下室 你给他打过电话
He went to the basement. You called him.
我没联系他
l didn't call him.
但他手机响了
His cell phone rang.
他说是你打来的
He said it was you.
地下室？
Basement, huh?
好的
All right.
保护自己 也注意下是不是我
Watch yourselves. And watch out for me.
萨姆？
Sammy!
萨姆 你在这吗？
Sam, you down here?
萨姆
Sam!
伙计
Man.
我叫你的时候回一声
Answer me when l'm calling you.
你还好吧？
You all right?
是 我很好
Yeah. I'm fine.
- 你知道那不是我打过来的 - 是 我知道？
- That wasn't me who called your cell. - Yeah, I know.
我想是什么东西想引诱我下来
l think something lured me here.
我想我知道是谁
l think I know who.
埃利科特医生
Dr. Ellicott.
这就是鬼魂们想和我们说的 你有没有看到他？
That's what the spirits have been saying. You haven't seen him, have you?
不
No.
你怎么知道是他？
How do you know it was him?
因为我找到了他的日志
l found his log book.
很明显 他在拿他的病人做实验
Apparently, he was experimenting on his patients.
可怕的实验
Some awful stuff.
在他眼里施行脑叶切开术 就跟吃阿斯匹林一样
Makes lobotomies look like aspirin.
但是病人自己骚乱的
But it was the patients who rioted.
他们因为反对埃利科特医生才骚乱的
Yeah, they were rioting against Dr. Ellicott.
院长在研究某种 超过人体限度的治疗方法
Dr. Feelgood was working on some sort of, like, extreme rage therapy.
他以为如果他能让他的病人 释放出他们的愤怒
He thought if he could get his patients to vent their anger.
他们就会被治好
They'd be cured of it.
相反这让他们情况越来越糟糕 也越来越愤怒
Instead, it only made them worse and worse, and angrier and angrier.
我在想 为什么他的鬼魂在做同样的事？
I'm thinking, what if his spirit is doing the same thing?
对那个警察 70年代的小孩
To the cop. To the kids in the '70s.
让他们怒气疼腾腾以至于杀人
Making them so angry, they become homicidal.
来吧
Come on.
我们得找到他的尸骨烧了它
We gotta find his bones and torch them.
怎么可能？
How?
警察都没找到他的尸体
The police never found his body.
那本日志说在这下面有间秘密的手术室
The log book said he had a hidden procedure.
用来对他的病人实施「治疗」
room down here somewhere…
所以如果我是个病人
where he'd work on his patients.
我把他弄到那里 然后以其人之道还其人之身
If I was a patient, l'd drag his ass down, do a little work on it myself.
我不知道 听上去有点
l don't know. It sounds kind of.
什么 很疯狂？
Crazy?
恩 就是这样
Yeah, exactly.
我告诉你我什么地方都找过了
I told you, I looked everywhere.
我没找到密室
I didn't find a hidden room.
这就是他们说的被藏了起来
That's why they call it hidden.
你听到那个了吗？
You hear that?
什么？
What?
这里有个门
There's a door here.
迪恩
Dean.
离这门远点
Step back from the door.
萨姆 放下枪
Sam, put the gun down.
这是命令吗？
ls that an order?
友好的请求
No, it's more of a friendly request.
我已经厌倦了你的命令
Because I'm getting pretty tired of taking your orders.
我明白了
I knew it.
埃利科特控制了你 不是吗？
Ellicott did something to you, didn't he?
为了你的命
For once.
请闭上你的臭嘴
Just shut your mouth.
你要做什么 萨姆？
What are you gonna do, Sam?
这把枪里装的是盐块
Gun's filled with rock salt.
它杀不了我
Not gonna kill me.
是的
No.
但它会让你痛的要命
But it'll hurt like hell.
萨姆 我们得烧了埃利科特尸骨
Sam! We gotta burn Ellicott's bones.
然后这一切都会结束
And all this'll be over.
你也会恢复正常
You'll be back to normal.
我很正常
I am normal.
我第一次说出事实真相
I'm just telling the truth for the first time.
为什么我们在这里？
I mean, why are we even here?
因为你像个小兵一样乖乖的听老爸的命令？
Because you're following Dad's orders like a good soldier?
以为你总是听从他的命令而没有疑问？
Because you always do what he says without question?
对于他你就那么奋不顾身？
You're that desperate for his approval?
这不是你本意 萨姆
This isn't you talking, Sam.
这就是你我的不同
That's the difference between you and me.
我有自己的想法
I have a mind of my own.
我不象你那么可怜
I'm not pathetic like you.
你想要做什么？
So, what are you gonna do, huh?
你要杀了我吗
You gonna kill me?
我已经厌倦了按你的话去做
You know what? I am sick of doing what you tell me to do.
六个月前我们根本没有靠近过爸爸
We're no closer to finding Dad today than we were six months ago.
好的 那就在这里
Well, then here.
让我释放你的愤怒
Let me make it easier for you.
来吧
Come on.
拿着它
Take it.
真的子弹比盐块好用多了
Real bullets are gonna work a hell of a lot better than rock salt.
拿着它
Take it!
你就那么恨我？
You hate me that much?
你觉得你能对你哥哥下手？
You think you could kill your own brother?
那就动手吧
Then go ahead.
扣动扳机
Pull the trigger.
开枪啊
Do it!
伙计 我才不会给你有子弹的枪
Man, l'm not gonna give you a loaded pistol.
对不起 萨姆
Sorry, Sammy.
哦 找到了
Oh, that's just gross.
撒上油
Yeah, soak it up.
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
我会帮你的
I'm going to help you.
我会让你感觉更舒服
I'm going to make you all better.
你不会杀我的 不是吗？
You're not gonna try to kill me, are you?
是的 很好
No. Good.
因为那听起来也很奇怪
Because that would be awkward.
谢谢你们
Thanks, guys.
谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
别再来闹鬼的收容所了 好吗？
No more haunted asylums, okay?
嘿 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
我很抱歉 兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
我在那里面的时候说了很多可怕的话
I said some awful things back there.
你都记得？
You remember all that?
是的
Yeah.
似乎是我不能控制
It's like I couldn't control it.
可我不是故意说 那些话
But I didn't mean it, any of it.
你不想那样？
You didn't, huh?
是的 当然我不想
No, of course not.
我们需要再继续谈论这个吗？
Do we need to talk about this?
不 不 我才不在乎那些情绪
No. I'm not really in the sharing and caring kind of mood.
现在我只想睡大觉
I just wanna get some sleep.
迪恩
Dean.
喂 爸爸？
Hello?
爸？
Dad?